all men get to this age now I don't know
if women ever get to this age let me
send me see of course you're not there
you're not there yeah I can't tell if
you're there you're there and this guy
you've been there for a while now what
age am I talking about him at the age
I'm starting to make noises when I don't
want to make news if I do any kind of
work around the house I make two noises
one noise when I do the work and then
another noise it's that second later and
it sounds like I'm thinking about the
work that I just did now I'll show you
and you'll get it watch this okay ready
that's we all on board
that's the whole joke right there
everything to noise I move a lamp a
mouse a little floor lamp I make noises
doing almost nothing sitting down I come
home at the end of the day I sit in my
chair at the end of the day never sat
down made a noise and if people concern
for your well-being after you make the
noise whoo are you okay are you all
right I'm fine thank you very much
I got my butt all the way back thank you
you know I won't tell all that you know
it's actually bad luck in show business
to reveal your age to an audience but
I'll tell you this I recently purchased
a bed the bed came with a 20 year
warranty and as I paid for it I'm
thinking to myself this is my deathbed
[Laughter]
so I'm getting a pillowtop I deserve it
I make noises doing almost nothing
adjusting the thermostat in the living
room now how much work is a thermos a
dials on the wall a little dial sounds
like I'm dragging a piano across the
room
[Laughter]
ah
man I love doing jokes and I do my
thermostat bit and you laugh because
that means you know what a thermostat is
like these are my people I'll do that
joke in Manhattan and get no response
because they all live in apartments with
radiators they don't know what a
thermostat is I better explain to
audiences like in Manhattan what
thermostats were like there were
children like there were little children
gather at my feet all right all right
listen up listen up no no no scoop
forward story time outside of cities
they live in houses yes they do they
really do inside their houses they have
a choice as to what the temperature is
going to be it's like science fiction
because you've never lived in a part of
the radiator not a lot of minut
temperature it just what the radiators
radiators are all are off the winter you
can either comfortably hang wrong meats
in the living room oh you're running
into your hallway on fire
the only way to adjust the temperature
and a part where the radiator is open
the window we have a landlord here
ladies and gentlemen yeah well the way
they raise and lower the window to
adjust the amount of the arctic air mass
the oil it is honey it's getting toasty
time for a nor'easter this kind of fight
is kind of funny I hope it is I'm at a
friend's apartment I'm in a friend's
apartment he's adjusting the temperature
with the window seat so it's a joke I
take a magic marker on the edge of the
window I just rode in
7876 74 that's funny right that's funny
I call that a Brooklyn thermostat that's
a brooklyn thermistor when I work up in
Canada I have to adjust that joke
cuz they're on the Celsius scale you
know because Canadians are very they
know Canadians are very earnest they're
good people but they take what you say
literally right now I'm over there I'm
going 7876 Canadian guy stands up you're
gonna
I love Canada my only problem with
Canada's their coins Canadian coins come
down and live amongst us I don't know
you folks if I get a Canadian quarter in
might change my day is shot cuz for the
rest of the day it's like I'm a kid I'm
playing tag and I'm it cuz I'm trying to
give it to somebody else
sometimes you got a Canadian quarter and
you don't know you got it
so it goes in your pocket you won't see
it all day you're gonna buy something
you reach in your pocket what you think
it's a regular quarter and you get this
other thing and they're deceptive same
size and the same weight but they have a
different picture your mind they'll try
and justify it oh my gosh I just noticed
apparently George Washington was a
transvestite
[Laughter]
my father my dad my dad used to make the
same noise when he'd adjust the
thermostat in our house
only then he'd look over his shoulder I
mean my dad used to go he go they look
over at me go back that thermostat I
think he thought I was somehow hooked up
to the thermostat and if they got the
temperature right I'd become the son he
wanted there you go that should do it
right there
no that ain't gonna do
hey did you know that Drybar comedy has
their own app download it right now to
watch save and share clips and watch my
whole special